datalot.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy - Datalot

### Privacy Policy

Thank you for accessing Datalot's proprietary online application (the "Platform"), either in demo mode or as a registered user of the Services (as defined below). The Platform is an Internet property of Datalot, Inc. ("Datalot," "we" or "us"). This Datalot Platform Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") outlines the privacy practices associated with use of the Platform. You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: (a) access or use the Platform as a demo, and at all times thereafter; and/or (b) register via the Platform to receive certain lead generation and/or call transfer services performed by Datalot ("Services") pursuant to the terms of the Datalot Lead Sales and Call Transfer Agreement ("Call Transfer Agreement").

This Privacy Policy shall be deemed incorporated into, and governed by, the Call Transfer Agreement and Datalot Platform End User License Agreement ("EULA"). For purposes of this Privacy Policy, the software, hardware, code, look, feel, functionality and any and all other aspects of the Platform shall be deemed the proprietary, Confidential Information of Datalot.

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, any reference to "you," "user" or "your" refers to you, the user of the Platform, and any employee, agent or third party that gains access to the Platform by and through your account. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety, you are not authorized to access or use the Platform in any manner or form whatsoever.

#### Personally Identifiable Information Collected

In order to access the Platform, you must: (a) provide us with your e-mail address; and (b) submit your password by and through the Platform. Where you request to access the Services by and through the Platform, you must submit your: (i) full name; (ii) billing address; (iii) credit card information; and (iv) any and all other information requested on the applicable registration form.

#### Sharing/Use of Personally Identifiable Information

As a general rule, and other than in connection with the limited exceptions set forth below, Datalot will not sell, share or rent your personal information to or with others. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Datalot may, from time to time, provide such information to certain third-party administrative service providers in connection with your request for, and use of, the Platform and/or Services including, without limitation, credit card payment processors. Any third-party so utilized by us has agreed to protect the confidentiality of the information provided by Datalot.

Further, Datalot reserves the right to share your personal information: (a) where required by law, or requested by a court of competent jurisdiction; (b) in the event that Datalot is sold or acquired; (c) where you are in violation of this Privacy Policy, the EULA and/or the Call Transfer Agreement; or (d) where Datalot determines, in its sole discretion, that such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights of Datalot and/or a third party, or necessary to protect Datalot from liability of any kind. The aforementioned includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

We use your personal information to facilitate your use of the Platform and/or Services and in order to process your request for Services. We will also use your personal information for customer service, to provide you with information that you may request, to customize your experience in connection with the Platform and/or to contact you when necessary in connection with transactions entered into by you via the Platform. We may also use your personal information for internal business purposes, such as analyzing and managing our business.

#### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you when you access the Platform. This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation, the type of browser that you use (e.g., Safari, Chrome, Internet Explorer), your IP address, the type of operating system that you use (e.g., Windows or iOS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Verizon, AT&T). We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Platform and to enable us to personalize your Platform experience.

When you access the Platform, we send a cookie and/or gif file ("Cookie") to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to your Internet browser. A Cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing non-personally identifiable information about you. Cookies have many benefits to enhance your experience with the Platform. To find out more about Cookies, please visit www.cookiecentral.com. To disable and reject certain Cookies, follow the instructions associated with your Internet browser. Even in the case where a user rejects a Cookie, he or she may still use the Platform. Datalot reserves the right to retain Cookie data indefinitely.

#### Deleting, Modifying and/or Updating Your Information

At your request, we will inform you of what personal information we have on file for you. In addition, at your request, we will remove, update and/or modify the personal information that you have provided to us, or that we have collected. You may do so by contacting us via e-mail at Privacy [at] Datalot [dot] com; provided, however, that we ask individuals to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes).

Please be advised that, after you delete your personal information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems.

#### Opt-Out/Unsubscribe

To opt-out of receiving Platform and/or Services-related messages from Datalot, you may do so by contacting us via e-mail at Privacy [at] Datalot [dot] com; provided, however, that you must cease requesting and/or utilizing the Platform and/or Services.

#### Minors

We do not knowingly collect information from individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. No information should be submitted to, or posted at, the Site by individuals under eighteen (18) years of age.

#### Security

We endeavor to safeguard and protect our users' personal information. When users make personal information available to us, their personal information is protected both online and offline (to the extent that we maintain any personal information offline). The privacy of your personal information is very important to us.

Where our registration/application process prompts users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card information), and when we store and transmit such sensitive information, that information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. Access to your personal information is strictly limited, and we take reasonable measures to ensure that your personal information is not accessible to the public. The servers that we store personal information on are kept in a secure physical environment. We also have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information under our control. Please be advised, however, that while we take every reasonable precaution available to protect your data, no storage facility, technology, software, security protocols or data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

Computer hackers that circumvent our security measures may gain access to certain portions of your personal information, and technological bugs, errors and glitches may cause inadvertent disclosures of your personal information; provided, however, that any attempt to breach the security of the network, our servers, databases or other hardware or software may constitute a crime punishable by law. For the reasons mentioned above, we cannot warrant that your personal information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through the Site is at your own risk.

All of our users' personal information is restricted in our offices. Only employees or third party agents who need the personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to personal information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all user personal information. Employees not adhering to our firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personal information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

#### Changes to Privacy Policy

Datalot reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice on the Platform interface that we are changing our Privacy Policy. If the manner in which we use personally identifiable information changes, Datalot will notify users by: (a) sending the modified policy to our users via email; and/or (b) by any other reasonable means acceptable under applicable state and federal law. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner, and we will only use your information in this different manner where you opt-in to such use.

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us at Privacy [at] Datalot [dot] com.
